[
  {
    "front": "diminui√ß√£o, redu√ß√£o",
    "back": "afname",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.802Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "sozinho",
    "back": "alleen",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.802Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "sempre",
    "back": "altijd",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.802Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "outro, diferente",
    "back": "andere",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.802Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "de outra forma, de outro modo",
    "back": "anders",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.802Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "pouco, um pouco",
    "back": "beetje",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.802Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "conhecimento, compreens√£o",
    "back": "begrip",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.802Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "telefonar, ligar",
    "back": "bellen",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "profiss√£o, ocupa√ß√£o",
    "back": "beroep",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "visita, visitar",
    "back": "bezoek",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "oferecer",
    "back": "bieden",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "morder",
    "back": "bijten",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "dentro, interno",
    "back": "binnen",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "soprar",
    "back": "blazen",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "construir, edificar",
    "back": "bouwen",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "quebrar, partir",
    "back": "breken",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "fora, exterior",
    "back": "buiten",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "escrit√≥rio",
    "back": "bureau",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Objeto dado como presente (üéÅ)",
    "back": "cadeau",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Figura plana em forma de c√≠rculo (‚≠ï)",
    "back": "cirkel",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  }
]